{
  "animal": {
    "name": "<colour:#4efc03><bold>Animal Quiz</></>",
    "questions": {
      "1": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Though they sound happy, what animal's \"laugh\" is a reaction to being threatened?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Ox</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Baboon</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Woodpecker</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Hyena</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["D"]
      },
      "2": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Capable of exceeding 186 miles per hour, what is the fastest creature in the animal kingdom?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Cheetah</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Peregrine Falcon</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Horse Fly</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Black Marlin</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["B"]
      },
      "3": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Known for its intelligence, which dog breed has been found capable of understanding more than a thousand words?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Cocker Spaniel</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Dachshund</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Border Collie</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>French Bulldog</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["C"]
      },
      "4": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Which animal species can live in extremes of both heat and cold, from -28.8 °C to 48.8 °C?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Bactrian Camel</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Chuckwalla Iguanas</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Polar Bear</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Emperor Pengiun</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["A"]
      },
      "5": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>The tiniest animal with a backbone is a what?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Fish</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Frog</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Bird</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Lizard</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["B"]
      },
      "6": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Growing up to 59 feet (18 meters) long, which is the world's largest living fish?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Manta Ray</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Marlin</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Whale Shark</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Sailfish</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["C"]
      },
      "7": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Which of these “fish” is actually a fish?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Crayfish</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Jellyfish</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Swordfish</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Starfish</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["C"]
      },
      "8": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>The largest “town” home to what animal was an underground colony measuring 25,000 square miles, found in Texas?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Meerkat</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Prairie Dog</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Capybara</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Beaver</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["B"]
      },
      "9": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>An individual animal of which type was found to be at least 272 years old, suggesting that its type includes the world's longest-living vertebrate?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Japanese Wagyu Cattle</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Indian Elephant</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Galapagos Tortoise</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Greenland Shark</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["D"]
      },
      "10": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>What gives flamingos their pink color?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Reaction To Sunlight</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Mud Captured In Feathers</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Eating Shrimp</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Dominant Genes</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["C"]
      },
      "11": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>A rattlesnake's rattle is made of the same material as what human body part?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Teeth</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Bone</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Fingernail</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Earlobe</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["C"]
      }
    }
  },
  "eurovision2025": {
    "name": "Eurovision 2025 Quiz",
    "questions": {
      "1": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Which song title is NOT from a Eurovision 2025 song?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Kant</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Maman</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>What The Hell Just Happened?</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Deslocado</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["A"]
      },
      "2": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>When did the juries vote for the Grand Final in Eurovision 2025?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>The evening before the Grand Final</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>During the Grand Final, right after each country has peformed</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>During the Grand Final, after all the countries have preformed</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>There was no juries 2025</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["A"]
      },
      "3": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>How many countries participated in Eurovision 2025?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>35</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>37</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>39</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>41</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["B"]
      },
      "4": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Italy's song for Eurovision 2025 is called ____</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Tutta l'Italia</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Zitti e buoni</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Quella diva</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Volevo essere un duro</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["D"]
      },
      "5": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Which sentence about Eurovision 2025 is True?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Poland's song is called \"Mila\"</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Bulgaria, Moldova and Hungary did not participate</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Montenegro participated after a 9-year absence</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Yuval Raphael has participated in Eurovision before 2025</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["B"]
      },
      "6": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>In which venue was Eurovision 2025 held?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>St. Jakobshalle</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Pala Olimpico</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Ahoy Arena</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Altice Arena</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["A"]
      },
      "7": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Which sentence about ESC 2025 is False?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>Emmy from Norway represented Ireland</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Sissal from Belgium represented Denmark</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Gabry Ponte from Italy represented San Marino</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>KAJ from Finland represented Sweden</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["B"]
      },
      "8": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Eurovision was held in Switzerland for the ____ time</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>First</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Second</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Third</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Fourth</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["C"]
      },
      "9": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>Who is Go-Jo?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>The official Eurovision Mascot</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>A rapper who represented Czechia</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>A singer who represented Australia</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>The winner of Festival da Canção 2025</>",
          "E": "<colour:#ffa24c>None of the above</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["C"]
      },
      "10": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>How many countries were pre-qualified for the Grand Final in 2025?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>4</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>5</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>6</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>7</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["C"]
      },
      "11": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>____ is a countertenor who was born in Vienna and grew up in Dubai</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>JJ</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>Red Sebastian</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>Adonxs</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>Klemen</>",
          "E": "<colour:#ffa24c>Princ</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["A"]
      },
      "12": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "<bold>How many countries qualified for the Grand Final from each of the two Semi-finals?</>",
        "options": {
          "A": "<colour:#00d2ff>8</>",
          "B": "<colour:#ff66c4>9</>",
          "C": "<colour:#90ee90>10</>",
          "D": "<colour:#ffa24c>11</>",
          "E": "<colour:#ffa24c>12</>"
        },
        "correctAnswers": ["C"]
      }
    }
  }
}
